Abdul Rafeh Fareedi

Mobile Application Developer

Mobile: +92 3101389789

E-mail: abdulrafeh46@gmail.com

Address: Multan, Pakistan



Professional Profile

A professional with 2+ years' experience. Analytical and detail oriented Flutter (Android & iOS) app developer professional with excellent communication skills. Worked on many enterprise-level projects ranging from development to product maintenance, new App structures, building new features, performing core updates, and code restructuring. This includes but no limited to,

- Knowledgeable about back-end development and documentation
- Analytical user of GIT version control implementation
- Consummate collaborator with clients, management, and team members
- Experience of using Trello/Zoho
- Interact with 3rd party APIs like Stripe/Firebase/Google Maps.

Skills

- Education: Bachelor's in Computer Science
- Tools & Technologies: Android Studio, VS Code, XCode, PhpStorm, MS Teams, Slack, GitHub, MS Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), Trello, Zoho
- Programming Languages: Dart, PHP
- Frameworks/Environments: Flutter, Laravel

Experience

Flutter Developer – Knarkz Solutions (July 2021 – Continue)

- Build cross platform mobile application for Android/IOS using Flutter framework
- Recent Applications

Note It Nip It (HR Application for catch bulling/harassment incidents)

Job Link (Location bases job search in the background)

ADIT Driving School (Driving school application for Teacher/Students)

Comply IX (Personal wallet for TAX payer for his/her tax forms)

Internee – Xufire Technologies (March 2021 - June 2021)

• Flutter & Laravel Developer (REST API)

IT Freelancer (August 2018 - March 2021)

• Web Developer

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

NFC Institute of Engineering and Technology Multan (2017 – 2021)

Languages

Urdu, English